Hands up! You're under arrest!
We're handing over two white boys
who would do the same thing
to us given the chance.
It's an investigation
that I need dropped.
Problem solved with one
interagency phone call.
- Which agency?
- The DEA.
I can offer 'em two Cali cartel captains
who are in Los Angeles.
- Oye.
- Come home soon.
What you doing with my rock?
Your rock? You out your goddamn mind?
You'll never be more
than Franklin's lapdog.
Lucia wanted the recipe.
And I said no.
So she must have got it from Kev.
- But Kev wouldn't do that.
- For Delroy's killer?
You're really gonna let Kev kill him
and start a fucking war?
Your boy's going to Acuña Park.
Stop. man. come on.
Kevin!
Stop! DEA!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hey. we need to call the hospitals
to see if he all right.
First thing we got to do
is we got to call Jerome.
Get his ass over here...
and Peaches. too.
Get him to dump that fucking car.
Hey. you do think he'll
be all right. right?
Of course.
I hit him in the leg.
He gonna be fine.
- Okay?
- All right.
Hey. hour's up. Time for another line.
Fuck.
Well. well. well...
what do we have here?
A game.
Supposed to keep making him snort.
or I shoot him.
I've played this game myself...
believe it or not.
And who are you?
Who the fuck is he?
I'm Avi.
I'm friends with Reed
and Matt. Who are you?
- Who are we?
- Yeah.
- Fuck you.
- That's who we are.
You remind me of a couple of
Lebanese pimps I used to know.
- Who you calling pimps?
- Who you calling Lebanese?
_
Carly. give me the gun.
Carly. if you move. you die.
Carly. if you don't give me
the fucking gun right now.
when I'm done with him.
I'm gonna feed you to the roosters.
Wait. wait. wait. don't...
don't kill her.
Reed's taking care of. um...
Of the problem. so we are
just waiting... here.
He'll have the money.
Just calm. calm. okay? Calm. yes.
What the fuck did you do to him?
We made him snort coke
for two days straight.
Force-fed him like the child that he is.
I keep waiting for him to die.
but our shit is so pure...
he just keeps fucking going.
Mmm.
You're the Colombians.
Sí.
So what happened?
Does he owe you money. too?
Yeah. we're supposed to
be in business with him.
But they keep canceling the shipments.
You know what?
I think...
we might have been looking
at this all wrong.
I mean. I love Colombia.
Turncoat piece of shit.
If I was there. I'd have
done that shit myself.
Ease up.
He was just doing what
he thought was right.
Anybody see it?
It was broad daylight at a busy park.
Don't nobody care
about a nigga shooting another
nigga in some Mexican park.
Yeah. but the cops. they
gonna talk to Kevin.
- You can bet on that shit.
- Kevin ain't gonna squeal.
He hardheaded. but he ain't no bitch.
That nigga gave up the recipe.
was ready to burn everything down.
You think he gonna keep
his mouth shut on this?
What he say might not matter.
There was a woman.
She came running at us
after it all went down.
yelling. "DEA. DEA."
DEA?
Where DEA come from?
Well. she see y'all. too?
She get your plates?
- Man. I don't know.
- We need to dump that car.
Already got Peaches on it.
Gun. too.
Well. will somebody call around
to see if Kev all right?
Okay. first. we gonna make
sure y'all all right.
Then we'll worry about Kevin.
Give me their names.
You hear me?
That wasn't part of my deal.
No. your fucking deal is
to provide information
that helps law enforcement
do its fucking job.
So you give me the fucking names.
or I'm gonna toss your immunity.
Okay. have it your way.
Wait.
I only know the name of the shooter.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Stay away from the windows. please.
I'm worried about Wanda.
I left her tied up at my spot.
Jerome will check up on her.
Yeah.
Hey. what'd you lie to us for?
I knew Kev couldn't handle it.
Man. fuck that. You should
have gave it to us straight.
Why we hiding out in
the cookhouse. Leon?
'Cause Kev listened to me?
No. 'cause he did
exactly what I'd thought
he'd do if he found out the truth.
Well. maybe you should have told him.
and the shit would've
went down different.
I mean. what if it was me that
got killed by that Mexican?
You would've let that shit slide. too?
If you had been as stupid
and dumb as Delroy and Vic.
going and selling after I
told you not to? Maybe.
- Fuck you. nigga.
- What would you have done...
send him after Conejo.
start a fucking war with the Eses?
If it was between my homey
and some random Mexican.
I'd have chosen my homey...
fuck the consequences.
Well. then it's a good fucking thing
- you ain't in charge.
- Maybe I should be.
Maybe Kev was right about your ass.
'cause look where the fuck we at.
- Stay away from the window.
- Fuck you.
- Hey.
I don't think there's a
telephone pole left untouched.
Alton. you think we crazy...
giving up a free house?
No.
Yeah. but...
you been homeless so
long. what do you care
if you don't have a roof over your head?
Still I rise.
I went and saw a one-bedroom
over on Hoover.
Needs a lot of paint and love.
It's got potential.
You know. that's almost
exactly what you said
when we moved in this place?
Cissy Saint?
Yes.
I'm Detective Avilés.
- This is Detective Stern.
- Ma'am.
We just want to ask you
a couple of questions
about your son. Franklin.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me. detectives.
Officer Andre Wright. South Bureau.
Mind if I ask what's going on?
You know that family?
Been knowing them my whole life.
This about the boy?
- How much do you know about him?
- Plenty.
And a lot of it lately hasn't been good.
_
Let's go. Avi. Vámonos.
Bueno. vamos. ¿sí?
_
Ya. get ready.
Set. set.
Go!
Ahh!
_
Was it two out of three?
Cops. Cops.
Cops. Shh!
Cops.
Well. get them the
fuck out of here. man.
It's your fucking house.
Um...
Good evening. officers.
How can I help you?
Are you the owner of this house?
Yes. I am.
It's my brother's.
but he's not home right now. so...
We received a noise complaint
from one of your neighbors.
Having a party?
Yes.
Just a couple of friends.
Sir. are you under the influence
- of any illegal substance?
- No. absolutely not.
I'm afraid we're gonna need
to take a look inside.
No. I can't... I can't...
I can't let you do that.
You can either move aside.
or I can place you under arrest
for obstructing an officer.
and then we're gonna go inside anyway.
No.
- No.
- Turn around.
Hey. no. no. officer.
- No. Hey.
- Turn around. turn around.
Tómela. Tómela.
Stop resisting.
- I have rights.
- I'm a veteran officer.
Hey. you really don't want to do this.
Shut up.
Step aside.
- Whoa. whoa.
- Uh. hello?
- Move aside.
- Sir. sir. sir.
Hey. Uh. evening.
Uh. this is... my house.
What's... what's going on?
Do you know this individual?
Yeah. Yeah. he's. uh...
he's my brother.
Do you know Detective William Han?
The Southwest Division?
He's a close friend of mine.
and before this goes any
further. I'd just...
- Stay there.
- I'd love to give him a call.
Make sure he's involved.
How do you know Detective Han?
We work together.
I'm with the State Department
here on assignment.
and. uh. he's our liaison at the LAPD.
I'd love to just give him
a call if you don't mind.
He can confirm everything I'm saying.
We'll radio back and try to confirm.
Mind if I hold on to your ID for now?
Yeah. absolutely. No problem.
Thank you.
Officer...
- The handcuffs?
- Wait there.
You okay?
I honestly have no idea.
We're going home.
What are you talking about?
We've been instructed to shut down
every facet of this
operation and walk away.
By who?
Operations Division Chief in Washington.
Did they tell you why?
No.
But I imagine they've got a good reason.
And you're not even
the least bit curious
as to what that reason is.
Honestly?
Not really.
You want to fight it? There's the phone.
Start dialing and yelling.
If it makes you feel any better.
we're not going away
completely empty-handed.
We've been alerted of two heavy-hitter
Cali Cartel traffickers
currently in Los Angeles.
Putting together a task
force as we speak.
Cut Lucia and Gustavo loose.
What?
Look. Franklin was right.
He had to do that shit.
He saved all of us.
Yeah. but I'm still
tripping on that DEA bitch.
How the fuck she get on the scene?
I don't think it was a coincidence.
- Hell. no.
- Shit.
We got to find out what they know.
They got Leon plate.
It's a matter of time
before they end up here.
Shit.
You know what?
I think I know who might could help.
Want me to come with you?
No. but pack a bag for Franklin.
'cause he gonna need
to lay low either way.
Franklin.
Franklin?
Where is he?
I have no idea. Why?
- Hey.
- Franklin!
- He ain't here.
- You know where my son is?
No. now. come on. She was
just leaving. Come on.
You think I'ma let you play
me like a fucking fool?
Listen.
- Everything all right. hey?
- Is it?
Is that why detectives are at my house.
telling me that Kevin's dead
and they want to talk
to Franklin about it?
What the fuck you... what
you mean Kevin's dead?
Shot and killed.
Now. you tell me where my son is
and what the fuck is going on.
Jerome!
Franklin gonna reach out to you
if he want to talk. all right?
Not having kids.
I get you don't understand this.
but that is not how parenting works.
Franklin ain't no goddamn child.
He is my child!
- He know what he doing.
- What you taught him.
Now I know you don't know
what the fuck you talking about.
Fuck I don't.
Him watching you hustle.
seeing the money and the girls.
You made him this way.
We all made him this way.
All of us.
You. me. Alton. Louie.
We all part of that boy.
Now he on his own path. and he gonna do
whatever the fuck he want to do.
At least I ain't turn my
back on him like you.
After everything I did for
you when you got here...
After everything I gave you...
Cissy. I paid you back years ago.
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
That house that your son
just paid off for you...
how you think Alton get the
down payment for that. Cissy?
You think he got the money
from flipping fucking burgers?
Hmm?
My fucking hustle.
You a goddamn liar.
Then ask your goddamn man.
'cause you ain't never believe me.
Don't matter where you got the
fucking money from. Cissy.
You took that house. you made a home.
you raised a boy in it.
I know you're afraid that
if you take Franklin money.
it's like you saying everything is fine.
but I'm telling you.
he gonna do it anyway.
If you can accept that...
he can still be in your life.
Well. now he's wanted for murder.
So he can't be in my life. can he?
Tell him I was here.
Jerome...
tell my son I was here.
I'll tell him.
Hey. hey.
Shit. Louie.
- You okay?
- Yeah. I'm all right.
That why we haven't seen you in here
the last couple of days?
Yeah. that's part of it.
We could have a chat with the
person responsible if you want.
You're about to.
But I ain't here to talk about Claudia.
I need a favor.
A friend of mine got shot
today in Acuña Park.
and I'm trying to figure
out what the hell happened
and they if they got any suspects.
And the detectives... they
ain't telling me shit.
I don't ask nothing for free.
I just need a little bit
of information. okay?
Nothing a couple easy-peasy
phone calls can't handle.
What's your friend's name?
- Kevin Hamilton.
- All right.
Thank you.
Want some?
Who you calling?
What you care?
Hey. Mom.
Hey. I was just. uh... wondering.
has anybody been at the
house looking for me?
Like. anybody?
Okay. thanks.
I don't know.
Look. can we talk about
this a little later?
'Cause I'm not in the
fucking mood right now.
Okay. Sorry.
Won't happen again.
I love you. too.
All right.
Here I am trying to see
if cops been in my house.
and Moms trying to score
some Stevie Wonder tickets.
If they ain't been there by now...
it means DEA didn't get your plates.
So we in the clear?
I've been thinking.
How you think the cops know
we was gonna be there to begin with?
Lucia.
She know we was going over
to the park to stop Kevin.
So you think she set us up?
She had the recipe.
Smart thing would be to
take out the competition.
Fucking snitch.
I'll tell you one thing. man...
we get out of this shit...
I'm gonna find that bitch.
I'm gonna find El Oso.
And we gonna have us a chat.
Hell. yeah.
That's it.
I don't front money ever again.
Next time you come up short.
my partners will pay you a visit.
Understood.
Go back to the hotel. make a call.
Guns will start making
their way to Panama.
Thank you.
We're gonna need to. um...
send a cleaning crew to the house.
pack that up... that's burnt.
Same thing with this place.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
I just need a little... I
just need a little more coke.
No. no. you need rest...
and medical attention.
Here.
Oh. Jesus Christ.
- Oh.
- Uh. uh... Here.
I don't feel good.
Okay. uh...
you got to take him to the hospital.
No. I'll lay down.
You go home. Rest.
Okay. um...
uh. yeah. take him home. put him in bed.
give him an IV.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
You did great.
- You hear me?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Come on.
Come on. Here you go. Hold up.
I got him.
God damn.
Where the hell y'all been?
Get my damn pages?
- What's wrong?
- What's up?
Kevin dead.
What the fuck you mean he dead?
Detectives went by Cissy house.
They told her.
Nah. They fucking with you. man.
Nah. I heard the same thing
from the two cops on Claudia's payroll.
His artery got hit. and he bled out.
Man. why the fuck did
you have to shoot him?
- Hey. hey.
- What?
Man. why the fuck did
you have to shoot him?
No. fuck this shit!
No. No.
There's more.
Cops got your name. Franklin.
- They know it's you.
- Man. fuck this shit.
What?
- Lee!
- No. just let him go.
You got bigger problems.
It's a murder beef now.
They got a federal witness.
We got talk about what
that mean for you.
For all of us.
Hey. babe. I got you some food.
Wanda!
Shit!
The cops gonna keep coming...
our place. Cissy's.
And he can't hide out here forever.
Where he gonna go?
I got people in Baton Rouge.
The boy just killed his best friend.
How he gonna handle that alone?
You think it's better he get arrested?
How long you think Franklin
gonna last in prison?
My people. they family.
They'd look after him. keep him safe.
Hey. baby.
How you feeling?
You hear from Leon?
That's gonna take a while.
The last thing Kev said to me was.
"You ain't built for this."
- Maybe he was right.
- Nephew...
Why else does shit go
down like this. huh?
It's the shit that I warned you about.
You want to make money?
You gonna deal with the consequences.
Ain't no way to get around that.
Yeah. well. I've always
known the next step.
Always known what I wanted.
And I can always get it.
But this shit...
I don't know what the fuck to do. Unc.
Baby...
maybe you just need to
take some time away
from all of this. right?
Just give yourself a break.
let the heat die down.
especially if we got
DEA snooping around.
That might be a good idea.
Your auntie. she got some
family in Baton Rouge.
I make one call. and we good.
I can get you out of here
tonight if you want.
I leave. what happens to the business?
You might need to...
put things on hold for a minute.
Hello?
Is that you. son?
If it is you. please. let me help you.
Come on. son. talk to me.
Tell me where you are.
Please. let me help you.
- Jerome and Louie?
- Sent 'em home.
Look. I'm sorry I lied to you. man.
This shit's all my fault.
Didn't find Wanda. so I
went out looking for her.
You should know. word's out.
Everybody talking about Kev being shot.
Talking about how you might of done it.
- Who's everybody?
- Lookout boys...
people selling. people buying...
everybody.
What they saying?
It's all twisted.
Some saying you shot him
because he tried to step up.
Others saying it's because of some girl
or he owed you money.
What you say?
I said you ain't do shit.
that is was LAPD setting you up.
Thanks. man.
You know. I might have to leave.
- And go where?
- Probably best you ain't know.
Look. I know this shit's a
lot. but I need a favor. man.
You think you can get me a car?
You gonna leave just like that?
What are you doing. Lorena?
You know this is why we got shut down...
him and his partner.
No. I don't.
And you don't either.
These people are seriously connected.
You keep after this. losing your job
is gonna be the least of your worries.
Honestly. Tony. at this point...
I couldn't care less about the job.
Thanks for everything.
Task force moves on the Colombians
tomorrow morning.
Sure you don't want to be part of that?
Happy hunting.
Oso!
_
You could've killed my kid!
Aah!
Oso.
- No. Oso. Oso. Oso.
- Ugh!
Quédate. Quédate conmigo.
- Quédate conmigo.
- Aah!
No. Oso. Oso. Oso. espérate.
Aquí estoy. okay?
Aquí me voy a quedar.
I'm right here. mi amor. Aquí estoy.
No. no. no. no. Oso. Oso.
Please. Oso. please.
Quédate conmigo.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
Yeah. just what you'd expect.
Both these squads know
they'll likely meet
again in the playoffs.
and they want to make a
statement here today.
Cody brings the ball across...
Nicaragua. huh?
That's interesting.
I'm sorry. You... Who are
you? You can't be here.
I guess the question is.
what agency doing work in Nicaragua
would want to shut down a DEA operation?
Oh.
You're the undercover at
the Villanueva place.
It's nice to meet you.
Guess I figured it was a guy.
Yeah. they usually do.
Looks like I caught you moving.
I really hope it's because of me.
You know. you wreck my
life. I wreck yours.
Right.
So. um... this has been fun.
but I think probably it's time you went.
I can just start guessing
if that's better for you.
Bureau of Intelligence and Research.
No. NSA. CIA.
I'm pretty sure you were told
to stop asking those questions.
And I will as soon as I hear something
that sounds like the truth.
Oh. the truth.
Yeah.
I think the truth is probably
that you and I are in this
for the same reasons.
Make America a better place.
Make America a safer place.
So why don't you go
ahead and explain to me
how you're making that happen
by shutting down my investigation
and I'll leave you alone?
I gave you the Colombians.
And how are you in the
position to do that. I wonder.
You do know about curiosity
and the cat. right?
I'm a dog person.
Your superiors don't know
you're here. do they?
My superiors don't much
of anything. Reed.
Well. maybe you were working
for the wrong people.
And what?
Are you the right people?
Maybe. I don't know. Maybe.
Or maybe I'm not a problem
that you need to solve.
Let's go for a ride.
Where are we going?
If I'm gonna tell you about all this.
I'm gonna need a drink.
So are you.
I'll follow you.
Any luck?
- Mama.
- Franklin.
Oh. God.
- I love you.
- I love you. too.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm okay.
Kev. he was...
He was gonna kill somebody bad. Mama.
Somebody who knew people
who might have come looking for payback.
Come after me. you...
everybody.
I didn't mean to kill Kev. Mama.
I didn't mean to kill Kev.
Uh...
look. I-I-I don't know
what might happen.
and I might have to leave.
b-but I had to see you.
I had to see you. and I had to tell you
that I don't want to
lose nobody else I love.
I thought I could do all of
this and help my people.
But it's not working out.
So I want you to know...
that if having you in my life
means that I got to stop all of this...
then I'm gonna do that for you. Mama.
Say something. Mama. please.
I just want to make
sure you're protected.
Cissy. it's Andre. Open up.
You go.
- I know Franklin's in there.
- Fuck.
I love you.
- Police!
- Let me see your hands!
Don't shoot him! Please.
don't shoot him.
- Don't move!
- Don't shoot him.
Wait. wait. please.
Don't shoot him. Don't shoot him.
- Stop resisting!
- All right!
Franklin.
- Come on.
- Stay down.
Franklin.
Stand up right now.
Come on.
I love you. son.
I love you.
I knew you couldn't stay
away from your mama.
I'm right here.
- Baby.
- Sorry. Mama.
I love you.
I'm right here.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-